thegreenhead.com 2019-11-03

# The Green Head - Privacy Policy

This document was last updated **October 19, 2019**.   
This Privacy Policy discloses the general privacy practices for **The Green Head - www.thegreenhead.com**.

#### SUMMARY

The Green Head is committed to respecting the privacy rights of visitors to any of its associated web sites. While visiting these web sites (collectively, the "Site"), we may ask you to register and/or provide information that personally identifies you ("Personal Information") for purposes of interacting with the Site. To further the protection of your Personal Information, The Green Head has adopted a set of information management guidelines, outlined below, that serve as the basis for our customer and advertiser relationships.

#### CHILDREN

No information should be submitted to The Green Head by children under 18 years of age without their parent's or guardian's consent. The Green Head does not monitor the age of its user audience.

#### AFFILIATE MARKETING

The Green Head is affiliated with several brand name online retailers, this is done either directly with the retailer or via a third-party provider of affiliate marketing programs. All links to online retailers may be automatically turned into affiliate links, which means that if you click through a link we post or purchase a product we recommend, we may get a small share of that sale from the online retailer. Neither the third-party providers, nor the retailers, share personally identifiable information with The Green Head. The information provided is generic in nature; type of product sold and date of sale for example. The information provided is not sold, shared, nor rented to any third party, and is used internally only. 

The Green Head is a participant in the Amazon Services LLC Associates Program, an affiliate advertising program designed to provide a means for sites to earn advertising fees by advertising and linking to Amazon.com. As an Amazon Associate, I earn from qualifying purchases.

#### INFORMATION & COOKIES

In order to perform certain search inquiries and handle the technological navigation through our web sites, we sometimes have to have a way to identify who has requested what from our website. We may do this, through means of a "cookie" which is used by The Green Head to identify certain technology settings. These cookies are only for use on our website and do not affect your computer in any way. 

We may use cookies to track usage of the Site and further customize your experience when you are visiting our site. By tracking usage, we can best determine what features of the Site best serve the users. We never give out information to others about individual usage. However, we may provide advertisers with aggregate information about our users, such as "100,000 people viewed your ad today.".

#### THIRD PARTY COOKIES

Some of our third party advertisers and affiliates may use cookies on the Site to track information such as the number of times an advertisement has been viewed (but not personal identifying information such as user names). The Green Head may give third party advertisers permission to set cookies for advertising, but The Green Head has no control over or access to such third party cookies.

#### WHAT CAN A COOKIE DO/NOT DO?

A cookie is an element of data that a web site can send to your browser, which may then be stored on your system. This element of data is a piece of text, not a program. The Site can only access the information from a cookie sent by the Site. We cannot access other cookies sent by other web sites nor the information contained therein. Additionally, we cannot learn your email address or any other information about you through the use of a cookie.

#### MAY I DECLINE TO ACCEPT A COOKIE?

On the pages of the Site that do not require registration, you may decline to accept cookies sent by the Site by selecting an option on your browser to reject cookies. However, some portions of the Site may require registration in order to access those areas. In such case, we ask that you register and provide us with basic information on our registration page. Finally in other cases, our website may not handle your "navigation request" correctly, without a cookie.

#### LINKS TO OTHER MATERIALS

If any link is offered connecting you to a third party web site, it is as an accommodation to the respective third party site owner and without charge. Third party sites linked to and from the Site are not necessarily under the control of The Green Head. The Green Head assumes no responsibilities or liabilities whatsoever for the content or privacy practices of any such linked site or any link or linking program at any time. The Green Head does not necessarily endorse companies (or related products or services) to or from which the Site is linked. If you decide to access any of the third party sites linked to the Site, you do so entirely at your own risk. The Green Head hereby disclaims any rights to trademarks, service marks, trade names, logos, copyrights, patents, domain names or other intellectual property interests of third parties.

#### COMMENTS

We only require a valid email address to leave a comment on pages of the Site. Your email address will never be displayed on the Site nor be disclosed to any third party. Comments that are inappropriate, purely promotional, vulgar, insensitive, all CAPS, unlawful or anything else we don't like, will be removed at our discretion. We reserve the right to remove any comments at any time.

#### USE OF PERSONAL INFORMATION

Personal Information collected or requested by The Green Head will never be given out to a third party in a manner that they can contact you directly. Any information provided to third parties is only in an aggregate form. We may disclose aggregated user statistics in order to describe our services to potential advertisers, partners and other third parties, and for other lawful purposes. 

This Privacy Policy only addresses the use and dissemination of information that we collect from you. To the extent that you disclose any information to other parties, whether through, for example, on-line auctions, chat rooms, personal ads, or the like, or through other web sites throughout the Internet, different policies may apply. Since The Green Head does not control the privacy policies of third parties, you are subject to the privacy customs and policies, if any, of that third party, and The Green Head shall not be responsible for the use or dissemination of your private information by that third party. Therefore, we encourage you to ask questions before you disclose your personal information to others. 

The Green Head uses reasonable precautions to keep the personal information disclosed to us secure. However, The Green Head is not responsible for any breach of security. If a Site user knowingly provides personal information, such as a name or email address, in a forum, comment message area or other public service, that user should be aware that the information provided can be collected and used by third parties. Such activities are beyond the control of The Green Head.

#### LEGAL DISCLAIMER

The Green Head makes every effort to preserve user privacy; however, we may need to disclose information when required by law. 

The Green Head may periodically update this Privacy Policy. If so, The Green Head will post the updated Privacy Policy on this site. We encourage you to review this Privacy Policy from time to time for any changes. If you have any questions regarding this policy, please Contact Us.
